myspace.de 2014-09-20

# Myspace Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy has changed. Please click here for a summary of the changes.

**Effective Date:** This Privacy Policy was last revised on June 24, 2014.

Myspace LLC (" **Myspace** ," " **we** ," " **our** ," or " **us** ") recognizes the importance of consumer privacy and we take this issue seriously. Accordingly, we have designed this Privacy Policy (this " **Policy** ") in a format that is easy to navigate so that you can better understand our privacy practices with respect to the information provided or collected on or through any of the Myspace Services that contain a link to this Policy. The Myspace Services are operated by Myspace, a company with a mailing address of 8391 Beverly Blvd., #349, Los Angeles, CA 90048, which is owned by the digital media company Interactive Media Holdings, Inc. (" **IMH** "). 

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with this entire Policy prior to providing us with any information through the Myspace Services. Throughout the policy we use capitalized defined terms. These terms are intended to have the meaning given to them in the Policy. You should read the entire Policy, but to facilitate your review, here is a partial list of some of the key topics that are discussed in greater detail throughout the Policy.

  * This Policy only applies to your activities on the Myspace Services that contain a link to the Policy, and it does not govern activities that are "offline" or unrelated to such Myspace Services. We encourage you to review the posted privacy policy on each of our websites and mobile applications prior to using them and providing us with information online.
  * We collect certain information about you when you interact with the Myspace Services ( _e.g._ , Usage Information), both by directly asking you to provide us with such information and by automatically collecting it, including through the use of Web Technologies. Some of this information may be shared with third parties, including other Users and Visitors, advertisers, advertising related service providers and IMH affiliates.
  * Third parties – including linked services ( _e.g._ , Twitter), advertisers, and advertising service providers may also collect certain information about you in connection with your use of the Myspace Services ( _e.g._ , Usage Information).
  * Your media consumption activities ( _e.g._ , streaming and downloading music, streaming video, IPTV, digital video, _etc_.) may be tracked through your use of the Myspace Services, subject to some limited preference settings. We may retain, use and disclose this media content consumption information as provided below for up to two (2) years from the date in which you consent unless you otherwise withdraw your consent. If we obtain a new consent from you after the date that we obtain your original consent, this period will be extended for additional two (2) year periods each time we obtain a new consent from you. Please review the terms of our Video Privacy Policy, which supplements this Policy.
  * You may be served with targeted advertising on the Myspace Services and on websites, applications, and other platforms owned or controlled by third parties based on information about you collected both on and off the Myspace Services, including advertisements based on your location and/or Usage Information.
  * Any information collected about you in connection with your use of the Myspace Services may be transferred to the United States. If you are based outside of the U.S., you expressly consent to the processing of your information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us here.

You can also print copies of this Policy by clicking [here](https://new.myspace.com/pages/privacy).

In the event you would like to receive a copy of this Policy by e-mail, please click [here](https://new.myspace.com/legal/privacy/contact).

## Privacy Policy

  1. Who We Are

Welcome to Myspace®, a place where people come to connect, discover, and share. Showcasing artists and their work, Myspace gives people access to a massive digital music library. With roots in music and social, the platform is built to empower all artists—from musicians and designers to writers and photographers—helping them connect with audiences, collaborators, and partners to achieve their goals. Through an open design, compelling editorial features, and analytics-based recommendations, Myspace fosters a creative community of people who connect around mutual affinity and inspiration for the purpose of shaping, sharing, and discovering what’s next. 

Myspace services include: (i) those offered on any Myspace-branded URL, including [www.myspace.com](https://www.myspace.com/) (the " **Myspace Website** "); (ii) Myspace messaging services (e.g., instant messaging, private messaging, public and private group chatting, etc.); (iii) Myspace music and video services (including, without limitation, any Myspace TV-branded video service (" **Myspace TV™** ); (iv) Myspace developer services; (v) Myspace mobile services; (vi) Myspace advertising services; and (vii) any other features, content, or applications offered or operated from time to time by Myspace in connection with Myspace's business, including when Myspace is accessed via the internet, mobile device, television or other device (collectively, " **Myspace Services** "). This Policy applies to the Myspace Services except where a different privacy policy is posted (e.g., the classic service at www.myspace.com and related classic mobile applications), in which case the posted policy applies. The Myspace Services are hosted in the United States.

  2. Scope Of This Policy

This Policy describes generally how we collect, use, store and share information that we receive from users of Myspace Services (" **Users** "). This Policy applies both to individuals using such services that register with Myspace and create Myspace Accounts and their associated Profile(s) (" **Members** "), as well as individuals who use such Myspace Services without registering (" **Visitors** ").

This Policy covers the activities of Myspace with respect to the collection, use, storage and disclosure of information through any of the Myspace Services that contain a link to this Policy. The activities of third parties or IMH affiliates that provide services (including advertising services) to Myspace, or that you link to from us, or that may collect information about you themselves or that we may share your information with, including our affiliates such as Specific Media LLC (" **Specific Media** "), are governed by the respective privacy policies of those third parties or IMH affiliates.

Please note that this Policy does not limit Myspace's use or sharing of aggregated, de-identified or other anonymized information that does not constitute Personal Information (as defined below). We may use and/or share such information in any manner not otherwise prohibited by this Policy, without notice or compensation to you, including freely disclosing for any legal purpose non-Personal Information to IMH affiliates, advertisers, partners, content owners, and other third parties.

We will continue to evaluate and update this Policy as we rollout additional services for our Users, employ new technologies and otherwise adapt and improve along with the evolving online and digital world so we recommend that you check for changes regularly. We welcome your comments, as we strive to maintain a Policy that is both transparent and that improves the Myspace Services.

To the extent that we provide you notice on any of the Myspace Services of different or additional privacy policies or practices _(e.g._ , at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.

In addition, please review Myspace Services' Terms of Use, which governs your use of Myspace Services.

  3. The Information That We Collect
    1. Information You Provide To Us

**Personal Information And Demographic Information**

We may ask you to provide us with certain information when you interact with the Myspace Services. This information can generally be grouped into two main categories - Personal Information and Demographic Information.

Information that identifies you as a particular individual is referred to in this Policy as " **Personal Information**." This would include your full name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. Please note that the term Personal Information does NOT include Myspace IDs or Device Identifiers (as such terms are defined below), except to the extent that they are combined with other forms of Personal Information that we have collected directly from you on the Myspace Services. The term " **Demographic Information** " refers to information about groups or particular types of individuals that access the Myspace Services. Demographic Information does not directly identify you as a specific individual, and would include information such as your age, gender, marital status, income level, and zip code.

We collect Personal Information and Demographic Information through the Myspace Services when you choose to provide us with such information, for example, when you register to become a Member. We may also collect Personal Information and/or Demographic Information through a variety of other methods, including when you elect to contact us, submit Profile Content or otherwise interact with the Myspace Services.

      * **Registration Information**

Certain features of the Myspace Services are only accessible by Members who have registered with Myspace and created a Myspace account (" **Account** "). In order to do so, you must first complete a registration form that requests certain basic registration information from you, such as your full name, e-mail address, date of birth, and gender (collectively, " **Registration Information** "). Please note that the Registration Information requested by Myspace may include both Personal Information and Demographic Information.

      * **Profile Content**

When you sign up as a Member, you are required to create one or more Myspace profiles that are associated with your Account (each, a " **Profile** "). Myspace may allow you to populate your Profile with certain content chosen by you, and we may also associate additional content with your Profile based on your interactions with the Myspace Services, such as your video viewing and other related activities (collectively, " **Profile Content** "). Any Profile Content that Myspace allows you to submit must comply with the restrictions set forth in our Terms of Use at all times. Please note that your Profile Content may contain Registration Information.

The information in your Profile Content is grouped into two main categories – Restricted Information.

" **Restricted Information** " refers to those portions of the Profile Content and Activity Notifications associated with your Profile to which you may elect to restrict access by changing the Profile settings that Myspace may make available to you from time-to-time here (" **Profile Settings** ") or by changing other functionality specific settings on the Myspace Services. These Profile Settings may permit you to create a " **Restricted Profile** " by choosing to enable certain (but not absolute) limitations on the availability of certain aspects of your Profile that are not Public Information, certain associated Profile Content, and some of the notifications that Myspace produces regarding your activities (" **Activity Notifications** "). Further, unless otherwise provided by Myspace, all of your Profile Content and Activity Notifications will still be available to the Profiles that you allow to connect to you. Please note you are currently unable to restrict access to Public Information, which can always be viewed, accessed, and used by anyone with access to the Myspace Services, including via third party search engines.

**"Public Information"** refers to the portion of your Profile Content that can always be viewed, accessed, and used by anyone with access to the Myspace Services ( _e.g._ , Myspace, other Users, search engines, advertisers, application developers, other third parties, etc.). Any Profile Content that does not otherwise constitute Restricted Information is considered Public Information for the purposes of this Policy. At a minimum, Public Information includes your:

      * Full Name
      * Username
      * Profile URL
      * About Me (the portion of your Profile that provides a place to describe yourself)
      * Profile Photo
      * Profile Cover
      * Stated Location
      * Gender
      * Age
      * Myspace IDs

**Public Information also includes:**

      * Any additional Profile Content associated with a " **Public Profile** ," which refers to any Profile for which a User has set the Profile's visibility status to "Public" in his or her Profile Settings, but subject to Mix privacy settings (as further defined); 
      * Activity Notifications published on the Myspace Services from Public Profiles;
      * Your status as a "Top Fan"; 
      * Affinity Information ( _e.g._ the relative magnitude of your affinity for Profiles and content); and
      * The number of your connections in and connections out.

You should be aware that the default setting for Profiles of Members who indicate that they are 18 years of age or older is public ( _i.e_ Public Profiles). The default setting for Profiles of Members who indicate that they are under 18 years of age is restricted ( _i.e_ Restricted Profiles), other than for Artist Profiles (as defined in the Terms of Use) of Members who are under 18 years of age, which are public by default. Other than with respect to Artist Profiles, whose visibility status may not be changed, you may change the visibility status of your Profile from a Public Profile to a Restricted Profile at any time by visiting Profile Settings. Please note, however, that Activity Notifications that were created during the time that your Profile was a Public Profile shall remain public after any change to a Restricted Profile.

Although access to Restricted Information will be limited as set forth above, it is important to note that if you share such information with others, they may copy that information or share it with others, including with the public. Myspace is not responsible for the actions of those with whom you choose to share your Restricted Information. For example, you may choose to use the Myspace Services to access content pages, which are those pages that, for example, represent an individual item of content such as video or audio, or a collection of content such as audio tracks ( _i.e._ , "Mixes$quot;). When you decide to post content, comments, or other materials to another Member's Profile, a Content Page, or elsewhere on the Myspace Services, that information will be disclosed, and available to third parties consistent with the visibility settings for the relevant Profile or content, **even if those settings are inconsistent with your own Profile Settings**. Content Pages are generally publicly available, which means that posts that you make on those pages will likely be available to anyone. In addition, your video viewing or audio selections may be part of your Profile Content as well as any content pages that you view. Similarly, if you connect to a Public Profile, the fact that you have connected to that Public Profile will be available to anybody with access to the Myspace Services.

The Profile Settings that Myspace makes available to Members, as well as their functionality, may change as the Myspace Services continue to evolve. We will provide reasonable advance notice of the changes in the Profile Settings section, or otherwise. Delays and errors in effecting Profile Setting preferences may occur and we do not represent that they will be immediate, complete, error-free, current, reliable or accurate. If you experience any problems with your Profile Settings, or have any questions or concerns regarding your Profile Settings, or you are interested in obtaining additional information regarding the settings options that may be available to you, please contact us at the Help Site.

The Myspace Services may allow messaging between Members. More information about who can message whom is available [here](https://help.myspace.com/hc/en-us/articles/202274374-Messaging-on-Myspace-).

More detailed information about Myspace's Profile Settings is available here.

**Account ID And Profile ID**

When you create an Account, Myspace assigns an " **Account ID** " to identify and organize information relating to your Account and a " **Profile ID** " for each Profile associated with an Account (collectively, your " **Myspace IDs** "). The Profile ID may allow Myspace to provide a unique internet URL for your Profile (" **Profile URL** "). As described above, Myspace IDs and/or Profile URLs constitute Public Information and may therefore be viewed, accessed, and/or used by anyone with access to the Myspace Services. You cannot restrict access to Public Information through your Profile Settings. 

    2. Information We Collect Or Store As You Access And Use The Myspace Services

In addition to the information that you choose to submit to us via the Myspace Services, we and our third-party service providers may also collect certain information about you automatically, including through the use of various technologies that passively store or collect certain information whenever you interact with the Myspace Services. This may include information about the nature of a User's interactions with the Myspace Services, such as his or her media consumption activities (" **Usage Information** "). Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies including cookies, web beacons, embedded scripts, entity tags and other similar technologies whether now or later devised (collectively " **Web Technologies** "), some of which may be downloaded to the computer or other Device. The Usage Information that we collect may be non identifying or it may be associated with you, your Account, and your Profile(s). In the event we collect certain information about your interaction with the Myspace Services while you are a Visitor, Myspace may associate that information with your Account if you subsequently become a Member. 

Examples of the Usage Information we may collect include:

      * your IP address or unique Device Identifiers;
      * your Device functionality ( _e.g._ , browser type, operating system, hardware, mobile network information, _etc_.);
      * the URL that referred you to the Myspace Services;
      * the areas within the Myspace Services that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences, which artists you are listening to, what videos you are viewing, or Profiles or content pages you choose to connect with, _etc_.;
      * your Device location (including using GPS and longitude and latitude location information);
      * your Device characteristics; 
      * certain other Device data ( _e.g._ , the time of day); and
      * ranking information about you with respect to other Users or content pages that you interact with ( _e.g._ , Myspace may record the links to content pages that you post and rank your association with that content compared to other Users). 

Please note that certain Web Technologies may set, change, alter, or modify settings or configurations on your Device. Additionally, third parties may use Web Technologies with the Myspace Services. We may not control those Web Technologies and we are not responsible for them. For more information on the options that may be available to you for opting out of Web Technologies, see Section 5. You can also avoid the Web Technologies used on the Myspace Services by not interacting with the Myspace Services and uninstalling any mobile or other applications for which Myspace is the application publisher.

More information related to cookies is available in our Cookie Policy. 

    3. Information We Receive From IMH Affiliates and Third-Parties 

Myspace may receive various types of information about you from IMH affiliates and from other third parties, including Demographic Information, Personal Information, web usage information, inferences drawn from that data, and unique Device Identifiers.

Myspace may also receive or collect certain information about you from third-party websites, platforms, or services in the event you choose to take advantage of various features that may allow you to integrate information on or to the Myspace Services. For example, Myspace may provide you with the option to voluntarily: (i) sync content from Twitter that will appear on the Myspace Services in your activity feed; (ii) authenticate your identity and register for Myspace using Facebook's authentication protocol; or (iii) otherwise integrate information from third-party sources. Similarly, we may allow third-party websites, platforms, or services to develop software applications that you can elect to install on your Account in order to provide additional functionality to the Myspace Services. These third party integrations and applications are collectively referred to in this Policy as " **Third-Party Linked Services** ". Should you voluntarily choose to take advantage of the Third-Party Linked Services offered through the Myspace Services, we may receive certain information about you from the relevant third-party providers, including the following:

      * Name
      * Nickname or username
      * Photo or graphic avatar
      * Unique third-party website identifier ( _e.g._ , Facebook User ID)
      * Biographical or Demographic Information ( _e.g._ , professional title, gender, college attended, etc.)
      * Likes and interests
      * Connections
      * Content accessed or associated with your third party service account ( _e.g._ , articles, songs, videos)
      * Any information that is publicly available on third-party websites
      * Device location (including GPS and longitude and latitude location information)
      * Other information that you choose to share with Myspace

We may supplement or otherwise combine the information we collect directly through the Myspace Services with information received or collected from IMH affiliates or other third parties.

Myspace will treat any information received from third parties (including providers of Third-Party Linked Services) as set forth in this Policy. However, the information practices of third parties are not governed by this Policy. Myspace cannot control the treatment of your information by third parties and we are not responsible for their privacy practices, which may differ from those described in this Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of any such third parties prior to choosing to integrate and/or install them on your Account or disclosing information to them. If you have any questions regarding a third party's information practices, you must contact the relevant entity directly.

For additional details regarding how the IMH affiliates collect, use, and share information, please consult IMH affiliates' privacy policies [here](http://specificmedia.com/privacy) and [here](http://vindico.com/legal/#privacy).

    4. Information You Provide About A Third Party

You may have the opportunity to communicate with others from the Myspace Services, such as by sending an invitation to a friend. If you choose to take advantage of this functionality, we may ask you to provide us with certain information about the person with whom you wish to communicate (e.g., name, e-mail address, mobile number, etc.). Myspace collects such information for the purposes of facilitating the requested communication, which may contain a specific promotional message from you (e.g., an invitation to register for the Myspace Services). Unless we explicitly say otherwise, Myspace will not use this information for other marketing purposes without first obtaining consent from the person to whom the relevant information pertains. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Myspace Services, your e-mail address, mobile number, name or username, and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies, as further detailed in Section 3.3 and Section 5.

  4. Myspace's Use And Disclosure Of Your Information

Except as otherwise set forth in this Policy, we may use the information that we collect about you through the Myspace Services for any purposes not prohibited by applicable laws and regulations, including as follows:

    1. Public Information And Myspace ID

Myspace may use and share your Public Information, including Myspace IDs, for any reason in our discretion. Public Information, including Myspace IDs, may be displayed in search results both on the Myspace Services and on external search engines ( _i.e._ , those owned or operated by third parties, such as Google). 

    2. Restricted Information And Other Information

Myspace may also disclose any of your Restricted Information, and any other information we have received from or about you, as set forth in the following subsections. In addition, Myspace may use and disclose your information for other purposes when you provide us with prior consent to use your information in such a manner.

      1. Restricted Information And Other Information

We may use any information we collect from and about Users in connection with providing and managing the Myspace Services. This may include, among other things: (i) measuring and improving the Myspace Services; (ii) facilitating your participation in online games, contests or promotions; (iii) enabling you to communicate and share with other Users; (iv) recommending content or connections (including other Users) to you; (v) analyzing and disclosing your ranking or affinity to certain content or Users to anyone; (vi) providing you with customer support and other requested services; and (vii) responding to your inquiries. 

      2. To Third-Party Service Providers To Assist Us In Providing And Managing Myspace Services

We may make your information available to our agents and service providers so that they can provide requested services on our behalf. These third parties assist us in providing and managing the Myspace Services in a variety of ways, including by: (i) developing or supporting products and features; (ii) supporting our marketing efforts (e.g., conducting e-mail marketing campaigns on our behalf); (iii) processing payments; (iv) administering message boards; (v) fulfilling orders; (vi) processing data or statistics; (vii) hosting media content; (viii) reviewing content for compliance with the Terms of Use; and (ix) assisting with the administration, judging, and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions, and sweepstakes. 

      3. To Third Party Linked Services

When you choose to use a Third-Party Linked Service, you are authorizing the Myspace Services to share information generated by or available on the Myspace Services, including Personal Information, with Third-Party Linked Services, including, but not limited to:

          * Full Name
          * Username
          * Profile URL 
          * About Me
          * Profile Photo
          * Profile Cover
          * Unique Myspace Identifier ( _e.g._ , Myspace IDs)
          * Stated Location
          * Gender
          * Age
          * Biographical or Demographic Information ( _e.g._ , professional title, college attended, _etc_.)
          * Interests
          * Connections
          * Any Information that Is Publicly Available on the Myspace Services
          * Device location (including using GPS and longitude and latitude location information)
          * Other Information that You Choose to Share with Third-Party Linked Services

Your decision to use, link to, install, integrate with or share with, a Third-Party Linked Service when accessing or using the Myspace Services is completely voluntary. Myspace’s sharing of information with Third-Party Linked Services from the Myspace Services is governed by this Policy. Myspace is not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices by the Third-Party Linked Service provider, however. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy and terms of service governing the use of the Third-Party Linked Service in order to understand how the Third-Party Linked Service will use the information you authorized Myspace to share on your behalf.

      4. Analytics Services

Myspace uses third-party analytics providers and products to obtain, compile, and analyze information (that may include your Profile Content (both Public Information and Restricted Information), Demographic Information, Usage Information and/or Device Identifiers about how Users are using and interacting with the Myspace Services. Myspace may provide such information to these analytics providers for the purpose of obtaining statistics and other information about how Users are using and interacting with the Myspace Services. 

These analytics providers may use their own Web Technologies to provide us with these services and may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including your Profile Content, Demographic Information, Usage Information and/or Device Identifiers. We are not responsible for those third-party Web Technologies or activities arising out of them. Some third-party analytics providers may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, some of which can be found here. We are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties' opt-out choices.

      5. To Allow Other Users To Find You

Myspace uses Public Information and Restricted Information in connection with User search inquiries to establish potential matches to search criteria using tools made available as part of the MySpace Services. We make good faith efforts not to display to other Users your Restricted Information except in accordance with your Profile Settings. Please note that Members under the self-reported age of 18 (other than respect to Artist Profiles for artists whose indicated age is under the age of 18 and may appear in people browse results) are not intended to show up in the results of Myspace’s “people browse” feature, which allows Users to browse for Members based on certain criteria inputted by the User. Please contact us here if you notice any discrepancy.

      6. To Deliver Relevant Content And Recommendations

To make your experience more interesting or relevant, we may use information you provide, or that we collect about you (e.g., Profile Content, including without limitation page views, queries, media consumption, and connections between your Profile and other Profiles or content pages), and information we may collect from other Users and third parties (e.g., Facebook or Twitter), to assist us in recommending Member and content connections to you on Myspace. Myspace may also combine your information with information collected by IMH affiliates or others to improve the Myspace Services and to make content recommendations to you both on and off of the Myspace Services.

      7. To Create A Social Media Consumption Experience

As part of the Myspace Services, your Usage Information and Profile Content (including video viewing and audio access) may be shared with other Users. To make your content consumption experience more social and fun, to improve services, to perform analytics, to compare your usage to other Users, to rank your linkages with certain content or Users, and to better make suggestions about other content, we may use any of the information you provide and the information we collect about you and we may share the content of the media that you access on or through the Myspace Services with other Users. We may also share your media access through Myspace Services (including video viewing and audio content access) as an activity notification by activity notification by, for example, sharing your Profile content (including your full name, username and Profile Picture) on the content page where such video or audio resides. Additionally, your activity may be indicated on your own Profile (in your activity stream or elsewhere) and on your connections' Profile, in each case, both on the Myspace Website, and on any other Myspace Services, including for example, the Myspace mobile App. Other examples of activities that may generate Activity Notifications include, but are not limited to: (i) posting status updates; (ii) commenting on a post; (iii) sharing content or posting on the Myspace Services; (iv) sharing content or posting to a Third-Party Linked Service; (v) connecting to a Profile or content ( _e.g._ , a photo, photo album, video, song, etc.); (vi) being tagged in a photo; (vii) commenting on a photo album; (viii) adding a photo to a photo album; (ix) playing a song or watching a video; (x) adding a song to a mix; (xi) updating a Profile; and (xii) adding a cover photo. An example of an actual Activity Notification on the Myspace Services is the following: "John Doe listened to the song 'True Love Waits'." Activity Notifications may include Profile Content ( _e.g._ , your full name and Profile photo), and some may aggregate your activity with activity of third parties ( _e.g._ , "John Doe and Sally Smith connected to a photo.").

**Myspace makes this feature public to everyone by default, and anyone can see these Activity Notifications**. Note that if your Profile is a Restricted Profile, the Profiles that you have allowed to connect to you will still see your Activity Notifications regarding your content consumption on Myspace. From time-to-time we may offer you with options, such as an option to opt out on a session basis, or a persistent basis, from Activity Notifications related to your content consumption. For more information, please visit here. Session settings are intended to last only as long as your Myspace page is open in your browser. If you close your browser, the session-based setting will be reset to public, and your song and video play Activity Notifications will default to the visibility setting associated with your Profile's visibility. **You should always check the content consumption Activity Notification setting each time you use the Myspace Services, so that you are aware of and comfortable with your media consumption appearing as Activity Notifications.**

We may use Usage Information (such as about your media consumption, connections to content pages or Profiles, and posts regarding content pages or Profiles), and your Profile Content, to rank affinity to other Profiles and content. This allows us to identify " **Top Fans** ", and we may use your Public Information to display that you are a Top Fan of an artist, other Profile, or a piece of content. Top Fan status is Public Information – anyone may see your status as a Top Fan. We also may provide analytics tools to Artist Profiles that allow the owners of such Artist Profiles to see Public Information of Users who strongly engage with the Artist Profile or the content pages controlled by the Artist Profile (e.g., videos or songs or such Artist Profile), including Users that are not connected to the Artist Profile.

**Unless otherwise noted, your consumption of media on the Myspace Services will be Public Information.**

**To Provide Activity Notifications To Provide Activity Notifications To Provide Activity Notifications**. For additional information on our video sharing practices, please review the terms of the Video Privacy Policy, which supplement this Policy.

      8. To Contact You

Myspace may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to Myspace Services or the services or products of Myspace's partners to the e-mail address you provided to us in your Registration Information or to the messaging functionality of your Profile(s). By maintaining an Account and/or using Myspace Services, you consent to the receipt of promotional materials or notifications to your e-mail address or Profile(s). If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from Myspace, you may unsubscribe by changing your Profile Settings or following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the relevant e-mail from Myspace. Please note that your opt-out request will not apply to subsequent or different subscriptions, or to certain transactional communications relating to your Account or use of the Myspace Services (e.g., administrative and service announcements). You may continue to receive transactional messages from Myspace even if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing or promotional communications.

For more information, please see Section 10 below titled "Managing Your Information On, And Communications From, Myspace."

      9. To Support And Improve The Myspace Services and the Services of IMH Affiliates

Many of the Myspace Services are free to Users because they are supported by advertising. We strive to make the advertising on the Myspace Services as relevant to you as possible. As a result, you may be served ads that are personalized based on, for example, your location, age, gender, content consumption, connections and other information, and we and third parties may use Web Technologies to deliver these ads. Additionally, we may share your Personal Information, Demographic Information, Usage Information, Device Identifiers, and any other information that we receive or collect with third parties (including IMH affiliates and our third-party advertising partners) in order to enable customization of the advertising displayed on the Myspace Services, other websites across the internet and other platforms, services and networks, including mobile and other connected Device platforms, and for other purposes not prohibited by this Policy. The parties with whom we may share your information may supplement your information with information they receive about you from others, in order to customize the advertisements they serve. They may also, in turn, share your information with others. If you do not wish for Myspace to use or share your information for purposes of personalized advertising, please click here to adjust your Myspace privacy settings. For additional information regarding the privacy practices of our third-party advertising partners, as well as the choices that they may make available to you, please click here.

      10. To Deliver Social Advertising To You And Your Friends

Myspace and Myspace’s ad-technology provider(s), including, for example, any IMH-affiliated company, and third-party providers, may also use Profile Content (both Public Information and Restricted Information) when delivering advertisements to you, your Myspace connections, other Users, and other users on any IMH-affiliated company advertising network or third-party advertising networks, including for example, by including your full name, username and/or photo in, or in connection with, sponsored content and advertisements.

If you do not wish for Myspace to use or share your information for purposes of personalized advertising, please click here to adjust your Myspace privacy settings.

      11. To Protect The Rights Of Myspace And Our Users, And To Comply With Legal Process

To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Myspace may also disclose User information if we believe in good faith that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Myspace or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Policy, our Terms of Use, and other applicable agreements and policies); or (ii) comply with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas, court orders or consent decrees). To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Myspace has complete discretion in electing to make or not make such disclosures, and to contest or not contest requests for such disclosures, all without notice to you. More information is available in our [Law Enforcement Guidelines](https://help.myspace.com/hc/en-us/articles/202248100-Law-Enforcement-).

      12. Business Transfers

Myspace may disclose User information in the event we file for bankruptcy, or in connection with certain types of business transactions that result in corporate change. For example, if Myspace is or may be (or substantially all of its assets are or may be) acquired by a third party pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, liquidation, or similar business transfer, we may disclose and transfer User information to the parties involved in the transaction ( _e.g._ , in connection with due diligence efforts or as a transferred asset).

      13. Co-Branded Areas

Certain areas of the Myspace Services may be provided to you in association with third parties (" **Co-Branded Areas** ") such as sponsors, charities and political organizations and will generally require you to disclose Personal Information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party and indicate if they have a privacy policy that applies to their collection and use of you information. If you elect to register for products and/or services, communicate with such third parties or download their content or applications, at Co-Branded Areas, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Further, if you sign-in to a Co-Branded Area with a username and password obtained on the Myspace Services, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the identified third parties for that Co-Branded Area. We are not responsible for such third party's data collection or practices and you should look to such third-party privacy policies for more information.

      14. Sweepstakes, Contests And Promotions

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (collectively, " **Promotions** ") through the Myspace Services that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules, such as on a winners list.

  5. Choices Regarding Third-Party Tracking And Targeting

This Policy discloses how Myspace collects, uses, discloses, and transfers your information and uses Web Technologies in connection with the Myspace Services to which this Policy applies. This Policy does not govern the collection, use, disclosure, or transfer of your information or use of Web Technologies by third parties. The collection, use, disclosure, or transfer of your information or use of Web Technologies by third parties is governed by the applicable third parties' privacy policies. Accordingly, you are encouraged to check those privacy policies for information about their individual privacy practices. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third-party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties. However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, some of which are available [here](https://myspace.com/pages/thirdparties).

For additional information on options for opting out of advertising by third parties, you may wish to visit [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices), or if you are a European user, [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

  6. Information For Members And Visitors Located Outside The United States

In certain countries, such as those of the European Union, you may have additional rights in respect of the processing of your Personal Information, including the existence of the right of access to and the right to rectify such information. You may also have the right to ask us not to use certain Web Technologies under our control or process certain of your Personal Information (or provide it to third parties to process) for e-mail marketing purposes. While these laws may not apply to Myspace Services, we offer certain options to non-US residents:

      * **Web Technologies:** By using the Myspace Services, we are seeking to obtain your consent to the use Web Technologies (other than such technologies that we consider as strictly necessary where we do not require your consent) by providing you with transparent information in our Policy and providing you with the opportunity to make your choice. If you do not wish to provide us with your consent, you may elect to disable Cookies (where not strictly necessary) by following the procedures identified in Section 3.2 above and our  Cookie Policy. Where the Web Technologies are used by third parties, then your choices are outlined in Section 4.2.9 and Section 5 above; and
      * **E-Mail Marketing Communications:** You will always have a right to opt-out from e-mail marketing communications. For further information on your right to opt-out from communications for marketing purposes, please refer to Section 4.2.8 and Section 10.

You can also exercise your options above, if applicable, at any time by contacting us in the following ways:

**By Postal Mail: Myspace LLC, 8391 Beverly Blvd., #349, Los Angeles, CA 90048; By electronic message at theHelp Site. By providing information to Myspace, you do so in the knowledge that the laws applicable in your home country may not apply to protect your Personal Information or to your use of the Myspace Services.**

**To the extent required by local law, by using the Myspace Services, you consent to the transfer of your personal data to the United States. If you do not agree to this international transfer of data, then you must refrain from using the Myspace Services.**

  7. How We Safeguard User Information

Myspace takes reasonable precautions to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information accessed, stored or transmitted by Myspace. 

  8. Protecting Children's Privacy

Myspace understands the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive world. We do not use the Myspace Services to knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If you are a child under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use the Myspace Services and should not send any information about yourself to us through the Myspace Services. 

In the event that Myspace becomes aware that we have collected Personal Information from any child, we will dispose of that information in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and other applicable laws and regulations. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 13 years old has provided us with information without your consent, please contact us here and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our systems. 

  9. If There Are Changes To The Policy

This Policy, your Profile Settings and your interaction with the Myspace Services are the primary means by which Myspace provides you with notice and choice regarding its collection and use of your Personal Information. 

Myspace may modify this Policy and/or Profile Setting options at any time. However, if we make material changes to this Policy that expand our rights to use your Personal Information, we will notify you either through a Myspace message, e-mail, and/or a prominent notice at the Myspace Website, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. You express your affirmative consent to any material changes if you choose to continue using the Myspace Services following notice of these changes in this manner. Your participation in and use of the Myspace Services is entirely voluntarily, and you may choose to cease to using the Myspace Services and/or to terminate your Account and its associated Profile(s) at any time and for any reason.

  10. Managing Your Information On, And Communications From, Myspace

We provide you with the ability, through your Profile Settings, to access, edit, or delete certain of your Registration Information and Profile Content. To do so, follow the steps outlined here. Please note that certain Registration Information is required to maintain an Account; therefore, if you desire to delete required Registration Information, you will have to delete your Account and associated Profiles. If you no longer want to use the Myspace Services, you may cancel your Account at any time. Even after you cancel your Account or delete information or Profile Content, copies of some information from your Account or Profile(s) may remain viewable in circumstances where, for example, you have posted information on another User's Profile, shared information with a Third-Party Linked Service, or if another Visitor or Member copied, stored or shared your information or has a copy of the link to content you shared on the Myspace Services. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may also retain backup information related to your Account and associated Profile(s) on our servers for as long as is reasonably necessary after cancellation for fraud detection, site operation or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. Please be aware that, due to the nature of certain internet and mobile technologies outside of our control, such as caching and networked technology, your Account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and there may be a delay in the removal of your information and content from elsewhere on the internet and from search engines. 

If you do not want to receive promotional (i.e., commercial) e-mail from us in the future, please contact us here. Myspace communicates with you for a number of different purposes. You may choose to stop receiving commercial e-mail from us for a specific purpose, multiple purposes or all purposes. You will also have the option of clicking on a link included in e-mail correspondence you receive from us in order to remove yourself from one or more of our types of communications. You may also opt-out of certain Myspace communications via Profile Settings here. Please note that there might be a brief delay between when you submit your request to "opt-out" and when it is processed and reflected in our systems. Accordingly you may continue to receive communications from us for a limited time after you unsubscribe. If your opt-out is limited to certain types of e-mails, the opt-out will be so limited. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain transactional communications relating to your account or use of the Myspace Services, such as administrative and service announcements even if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing or promotional communications. 

  11. How To Contact Us

If you have questions about this Policy or any complaints about our procedures, please contact Myspace at:

## Key Terms

**Cookies**. A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Myspace Services. A Flash cookie (or locally shared object) is a data file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device. HTML5 cookies can be programmed through HTML5 local storage. Unlike Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies do not require a plug-in. Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial internet browsers, and in some instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies or HTML5 cookies. For information on disabling Flash cookies go to Adobe's website [www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/). Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies, Flash cookies, or HTML5 cookies on your Device, some parts of the Myspace Services may not function properly, and that when you revisit the Myspace Services your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.

**Device.** The personal computer, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other handheld device, internet connected television or other device that you use to access the Myspace Services.

**Device Identifier.** A unique string of numbers, letters or characters that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Myspace Services that allows our servers to identify your Device.

**Embedded Scripts**. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Myspace Services, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Myspace Services, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**ETag, or entity tag**. A feature of the cache in browsers. It is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are a form of Device Identifier. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash, and/or HTML5 cookies.

**Web Beacons**. Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as "1x1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs") may be included in the Myspace Services' pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including to: count visitors to the Myspace Services, to monitor how users navigate the Myspace Services, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.
